Guide to the International Brigades Archive, Moscow: Selected Images ALBA.PHOTO.177
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Folder 178: Undated Photographs
  - [Group shot, soldiers against a building], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178016)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/16
  - [Soldiers reading letters], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178017)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/17
  - [Soldiers receiving supplies (?) from man with car], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178018)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/18
  - [Soldier reading letter in a trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178019)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/19
  - [Soldier hands out a parcel], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178020)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/20
  - [Group shot of soldiers], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178021)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/21
  - [Four soldiers in combat gear], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178022)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/22
  - [Three soldiers, on handing a cigarette to another], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178023)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/23
  - [Candid group shot of soldiers], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178024)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/24
  - [Men gathered in camp, one with bandaged head], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178025)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/25
  - [Alley with piles of clothes on ground and on a table; distribution (?)], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178026)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/26
  - [Men putting on uniforms (?)], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178027)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/27
  - Mother Bloor, American Revolutionary (76th Birthday Celebration), undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178028)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/28
  - ["Maximville" campsite; Tents and "Mother Bloor" banner], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178029)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/29
  - [Group of soldiers], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178030)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/30
  - [Over-the-shoulder shot of soldiers gathered in combat gear], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178031)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/31
  - [Two men looking at a document, undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178032)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/32
  - [Officer in group of soldiers], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178033)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/33
  - [Seated man workin in a communication post], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178034)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/34
  - [Two soldiers in foreground, armored vehicle in background], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178035)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/35
  - [Soldiers pose in trench with rifles and banner], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178036)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/36
  - [Man in suit addresses troops at night], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178037)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/37
  - [Column of troops marching through a city], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178038)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/38
  - Ivan Fajorda and Pol[itical]-Comm[issar] of Company 1, Killed in Action (Villanueva de Canada), undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178039)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/39
  - Ralph Bates (Speaking to Drivers of 1st Regiment de Tren, 5th Army Corps, 2 Squadron), undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178040)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/40
  - [Two men in front of sandbag wall], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178041)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/41
  - [Soldier standing in the trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178042)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/42
  - [Casual group pose], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178043)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/43
  - [Troops in a trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178044)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/44
  - [Troops on the march], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178045)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/45
  - [Small rockwall/sandbag area under a tree], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178046)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/46
  - [Troops sitting and climbing on rocky hillside], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178047)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/47
  - [Three soldiers reading], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178048)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/48
  - [Officer addressing three soldiers], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178049)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/49
  - [Flock of sheep, soldiers with tripods, church in distance], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178050)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/50
  - [Group of soldiers on horseback], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178051)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/51
  - [Large group of soldiers assembled in a plaza], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178052)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/52
  - [Soldiers in group in front of brick wall], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178053)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/53
  - [Soldiers carrying bread, pail, basin, spoons], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178054)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/54
  - [Two soldiers inspecting rolled-up documents at an outpost], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178055)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/55
  - [Soldier in trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178056)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/56
  - [Soldier poses in trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178057)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/57
  - Major Fort of 15th International Brigade, undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178058)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/58
  - [Bearded soldier with leather jacket], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178059)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/59
  - [Small group of troops in trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178060)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/60
  - [Troops in trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178061)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/61
  - [Troops in trench. Dup of 178061], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178062)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/62
  - [Troops in trench with rifles], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178063)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/63
  - [Group shot, soldiers with musical instruments. Includes same group as in 178010], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178064)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/64
  - [Soldiers posed by trench, some in overcoats], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178065)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/65
  - [Soldiers with machinery/weapons in trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178066)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/66
  - [Two men on a path], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178067)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/67
  - [Soldier works at typewriter, portraits of communist notables hang overhead], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178068)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/68
  - [Soldier with rifle in a tiny shelter], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178069)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/69
  - [Soldiers in trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178070)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/70
  - [Group shot in front of sandbags], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178071)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/71
  - [Men working in trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178072)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/72
  - [Troops pose in trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178073)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/73
  - [Officer and troops near a dugout and a tree], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178074)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/74
  - [Three soldiers with a machine gun], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178075)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/75
  - [Soldiers in a trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178076)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/76
  - [Two soldiers pose under a tree], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178077)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/77
  - [Soldiers with machinery/weapon in trench. Same group as 178066], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178078)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/78
  - [Small group of soldiers], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178079)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/79
  - [Officer and soldier conversing in a trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178080)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/80
  - [Memorial marker: "To our fallen comrades our victory is your vengeance. June 1937"], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178081)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/81
  - [Men in civilian clothes, sign with arrow], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178082)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/82
  - [Soldiers lined up], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178083)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/83
  - [Wide shot mass of troops, working, against mountain backdrop], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178084)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/84
  - [Soldiers converse with officer in a trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178085)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/85
  - [Soldiers digging a trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 177_178086)
    Moscow Number: 5/178/86
- Folder 179: Photo Album of 15th International Brigade in Preparation for Brunete Offensive; Photographed by Yugoslavian Volunteer, Major Vladimir Stefanovich
  - [Wounded soldier lying on a cot], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179001)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/1
  - [Three soldiers leaning against trench wall; one reading], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179002)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/2
  - [Wounded soldier lying on a cot], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179003)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/3
  - [Group of four soldiers poses by tree], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179004)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/4
  - [Troops lined up for instruction/inspection], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179005)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/5
  - [Posed group shot of soldiers outdoors], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179006)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/6
  - [Large group of soldiers assembled], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179007)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/7
  - [Soldiers in a group pose by a tree], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179008)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/8
  - [Open field, truck, trees, hill in the background], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179009)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/9
  - [Truck hidden in brush], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179010)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/10
  - [Trucks placed among low-lying trees], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179011)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/11
  - [Troops showering outdoors, shower system attached to truck], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179012)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/12
  - [Large buildings seen from across a field], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179013)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/13
  - [Troops showering outdoors with truck shower system], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179014)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/14
  - [Stone hut on hillside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179015)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/15
  - [Troops showering outdoors using truck shower system], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179016)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/16
  - [Trucks coming down the road], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179017)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/17
  - [Barren hillside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179018)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/18
  - [Two men putting foliage in the back of a truck], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179019)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/19
  - [Transport vehicles among small trees], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179020)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/20
  - [Soldiers in town with a group of women and children], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179021)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/21
  - [Large mass of soldiers on the edge of town], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179022)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/22
  - [Men sitting/standing around, some wearing swimming trunks], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179023)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/23
  - [Men with transport vehicles in town], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179024)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/24
  - [Mass of soldiers mixing with civilians], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179025)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/25
  - [Logs lay by roadside, distant mountains], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179026)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/26
  - [Rocky hillside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179027)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/27
  - [Men working in town, building/repairing a road], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179028)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/28
  - [Three soldiers seated against trench wall], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179029)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/29
  - [Man sitting with newspapers, typewriter spread on ground around him], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179030)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/30
  - [Four soldiers smile for camera, trucks in background], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179031)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/31
  - [An officer and two soldiers pose], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179032)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/32
  - [Rubble in front of entrance to chapel], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179033)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/33
  - [Rubble and destroyed buildings], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179034)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/34
  - [Woman and four children. Soldiers and other children visible in background], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179035)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/35
  - [Man in shorts drinks from a goblet], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179036)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/36
  - [Troops along roadside, some shirtless], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179037)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/37
  - [Shirtless troops seated in shade of a tree], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179038)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/38
  - [Soldier stripped to underpants grooming himself, using mirror hung on a tree], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179039)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/39
  - [Man sits on ground, eating], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179040)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/40
  - [Open countryside, troops and a truck visible], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179041)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/41
  - [Man sleeping on floor], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179042)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/42
  - [Truck underneath a tree, men rest against it], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179043)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/43
  - [Man works at typewriter in communications post], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179044)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/44
  - [Tree-dotted countryside, truck midground], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179045)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/45
  - [Rugged open countryside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179046)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/46
  - [Field with line of trees], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179047)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/47
  - [Tree-dotted countryside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179048)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/48
  - [Soldier with beret], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179049)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/49
  - [Bearded soldier poses with hand on hip], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179050)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/50
  - [Officer in camp, other men sitting on the ground around him], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179051)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/51
  - [Officer poses], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179052)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/52
  - [Officer with jacket on], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179053)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/53
  - [Soldier poses and smiles], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179054)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/54
  - [Pollitt speaks to troops in front of transport vehicle], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179055)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/55
  - [African-American soldier poses seated on a stone wall], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179056)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/56
  - [Large group pose with Spanish flag], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179061)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/61
  - [Large crowded group shot of soldiers with some civilians], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179062)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/62
  - [Group shot soldiers and officers forest background], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179063)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/63
  - [Group shot troops hillside background], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179064)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/64
  - [Rugged hillside, a figure visible at the top], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179065)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/65
  - [Rugged hillside, soldier running by bottom right corner], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179066)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/66
  - [Small group gathered on hillside path with a horse], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179067)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/67
  - [Troops up ahead on a hilly path], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179068)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/68
  - [Troops at a rocky outcropping with supplies], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179069)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/69
  - [Hillside dotted with trees], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179070)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/70
  - [Open field with distant trees], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179071)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/71
  - [Open countryside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179072)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/72
  - [Three soldiers resting in the shade of a tree], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179073)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/73
  - [Soldiers resting in a ditch on the hillside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179074)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/74
  - [Two helmeted soldiers, one of them is African-American], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179075)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/75
  - [Two soldiers relaxing and having a cigarette], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179076)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/76
  - [Dirt road heading into a settlement], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179081)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/81
  - [Wall outlining ruined settlement], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179082)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/82
  - [Open field, structure visible on the horizon], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179083)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/83
  - [Tattered barbed-wire fencing], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179084)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/84
  - [Men laying in a trench, some sleeping], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179085)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/85
  - [Soldier smoking cigarette next to sleeping men in trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179086)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/86
  - [Troops seated in deep trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179087)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/87
  - [Three men eating, one man writing, outdoors], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179088)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/88
  - [Open countryside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179089)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/89
  - [Open field, cloud of smoke (?) on horizon], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179090)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/90
  - [Motorcycle parked under a tree], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179091)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/91
  - [Rubble on a dirt road], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179092)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/92
  - [Open plain to rising hills in the distance], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179093)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/93
  - [Road along the hillside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179094)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/94
  - [Open plain to rising hills in the distance], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179095)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/95
  - [Open plain to rising hills in the distance], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179096)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/96
  - [Open plain to rising hills in the distance], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179097)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/97
  - [Open plain to rising hills in the distance], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179098)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/98
  - [Open plain to rising hills in the distance], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179099)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/99
  - [Open plain], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179100)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/100
  - [Ravine with dense foliage], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179101)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/101
  - [Troops loading up the back of a truck], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179102)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/102
  - [Six soldiers huddled in conversation], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179103)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/103
  - [Crowd of troops, most looking away from camera, in line for a meal], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179104)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/104
  - [Four men relax under a bush], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179105)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/105
  - [Men relax under a tree next to stone wall along a road], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179106)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/106
  - [Troops resting on ground under blankets], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179107)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/107
  - [Seated soldiers gathered around in bushes and small trees], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179108)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/108
  - [Aerial view of countryside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179109)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/109
  - [Aerial view of countryside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179110)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/110
  - [Open plain], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179111)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/111
  - [Rocky open plain], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179112)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/112
  - [Five soldiers smile for camera while resting under a tree], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179113)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/113
  - [Three seated soldiers with helmets on], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179114)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/114
  - [Troops taking a rest against a hillside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179115)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/115
  - [Soldier laying down for a rest], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179116)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/116
  - [Soldier in a dug-out hole, reading a newspaper], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179121)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/121
  - [Men standing around in a trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179122)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/122
  - [Men sitting, reading in a trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179123)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/123
  - [Men sitting, talking in trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179124)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/124
  - [Open countryside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179125)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/125
  - [Open countryside, brush/low-lying foliage], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179126)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/126
  - [Open countryside, field with tree and boulders], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179127)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/127
  - [Small trees on hillside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179128)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/128
  - [Camoflaged camp site with troops], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179129)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/129
  - [Troops sitting around in camp, one lights another's cigarette], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179130)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/130
  - [Wide shot troops sitting in camp], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179131)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/131
  - [Countryside covered with scrubby foliage], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179132)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/132
  - [Tree-dotted landscape], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179133)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/133
  - [Tree-dotted landscape], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179134)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/134
  - [Field with trees], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179135)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/135
  - [Field with big trees, small bushes], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179136)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/136
  - [Open countryside (hard to see)], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179137)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/137
  - [Camoflaged camp site with troops], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179138)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/138
  - [Cloudy sky, treetop visible in bottom of frame], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179139)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/139
  - [Crude shelter under a small tree], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179140)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/140
  - [Men resting, seated, next to a small stream], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179141)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/141
  - [Men sitting in camp, writing letters], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179142)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/142
  - [Several troops sit in the shade], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179143)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/143